Speaker: Part 2
Mrs Myers turned over the first card.
‘The seven of diamonds. That means money. You’re going to be rich!
And the jack of hearts! That’s a lovely card.
It means you’re going to meet a young man.’
‘Ah,’ said Mrs McCleary. ‘And what next?’
‘The ten of spades,’ said Mrs Myers, as she turned over the third card.
‘That means you’re going to travel. But then,’ she exclaimed,
‘we’ve got the king of clubs! Clubs always mean problems.
Somebody’s going to try to stop you. An old man…’
‘Probably my father!’ Mrs McCleary exclaimed.
‘But let’s look at the last card,’ said Mrs Myers.
‘The queen of hearts! You’re going to fall in love with a young man.
Dear Miss Jones, in one year’s time you’re going to marry a very rich young man,
a businessman – he travels a lot.
An old man is going to try to stop your marriage, but he’s not going to succeed.
You’re going to move far away from here, probably abroad.
That will be one pound, please.’
‘Thank you so much,’ said Mrs McCleary.
She took a pound from her purse and gave it to Mrs Myers.
‘Thank you,’ said Mrs Myers.
‘Goodbye, my dear Miss Jones…Next please!’
When Mrs McCleary got home, she told her husband everything.
‘I don’t like it,’ Inspector McCleary said. ‘What shall we do about her?
I know! I’ll report her.’
And that’s what Inspector McCleary did.